
Loading model... 


▄▄ ▄▄
██ ██
██ ██  ▀▀█▄ ███▄███▄  ▀▀█▄    ▄████ ████▄ ████▄
██ ██ ▄█▀██ ██ ██ ██ ▄█▀██    ██    ██ ██ ██ ██
██ ██ ▀█▄██ ██ ██ ██ ▀█▄██ ██ ▀████ ████▀ ████▀
                                    ██    ██
                                    ▀▀    ▀▀

build      : b9219-45b455e66
model      : Qwen3.6-27B-abliterated-Gaston-MTP-Q4_K_M.gguf
modalities : text

available commands:
  /exit or Ctrl+C     stop or exit
  /regen              regenerate the last response
  /clear              clear the chat history
  /read <file>        add a text file
  /glob <pattern>     add text files using globbing pattern


> In three short sentences, explain why memory bandwidth matters for local LLM inference.

Large language models require massive amounts of data to be transferred from RAM to the processor for every single token generated, making the speed of this transfer the primary bottleneck. Unlike compute-bound tasks, local LLM inferencing is almost entirely memory-bandwidth-bound, meaning raw processing power is often underutilized while waiting for data. Consequently, higher memory bandwidth directly correlates with faster text generation speeds and a smoother user experience on consumer hardware.

[ Prompt: 77.7 t/s | Generation: 11.9 t/s ]

Exiting...
