
Loading model... 


▄▄ ▄▄
██ ██
██ ██  ▀▀█▄ ███▄███▄  ▀▀█▄    ▄████ ████▄ ████▄
██ ██ ▄█▀██ ██ ██ ██ ▄█▀██    ██    ██ ██ ██ ██
██ ██ ▀█▄██ ██ ██ ██ ▀█▄██ ██ ▀████ ████▀ ████▀
                                    ██    ██
                                    ▀▀    ▀▀

build      : b9219-45b455e66
model      : Qwen3.6-27B-abliterated-Gaston-MTP-Q4_K_M.gguf
modalities : text

available commands:
  /exit or Ctrl+C     stop or exit
  /regen              regenerate the last response
  /clear              clear the chat history
  /read <file>        add a text file
  /glob <pattern>     add text files using globbing pattern


> In three short sentences, explain why memory bandwidth matters for local LLM inference.

Local LLMs require massive amounts of VRAM to store model weights, making the speed at which this data can be read the primary bottleneck for generation. Since the GPU cores often sit idle while waiting for parameters to arrive, increasing memory bandwidth directly accelerates the token-per-seconds output rate. Consequently, optimizing for high bandwidth is more critical for latency than raw compute power when running models on consumer hardware.

[ Prompt: 32.0 t/s | Generation: 15.2 t/s ]

Exiting...
